Hamada ali

Web Developer Two Years experience Flutter Developer One Year experience

Address:

Cairo - Nasr city - Egypt

Phone:

+201150769418

Email:

hamadaali221133@gmail.com

Summary

Web Developer specializing in backe end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Flutter Developer specializing in developing mobile applications. Experienced in the development of mobile application projects, Well-versed in Firebase, working with REST APIs state management provider, SQFLITE.

Skill Highlights

- Dart Flutter
- HTML&CSS
- Javascript&Jquery&Bootstra
- PHP&OOP&PDO&MYSQL
- Laraval5
- Wordpress

Experience

php Wordpress Developer - 06/2016 to 05/2017 techVillgeco company , New Cairo PHP Laravel Developer - 01/2018 to 05/2019

Matrix Couds company, New Cairo

- maintain optimal workflow.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

Dart Flutter Developer - 01/2018 to 05/2019

FreeLancer, Work from home

- I uploaded two applications to the Play Store.
- maintain optimal workflow.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- I uploaded two applications to the Play Store.

Education

Bachelor of Science: **Computer Information Systems** - 2016 **Graduate from High Institute for Computer Information s**

My previous work

Flutter App:

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.maojod.maojod_app

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1UgfRaZvj7KcxJbaRI0fNLBmw_HV8oyEN/view?usp=sharing

https://drive.google.com/file/d/13tjBY_2R4vARseHxt-jWsvdbw-hIp8FM/view?usp=sharing

https://file.fm/u/qdy2cpv4

Web Sites:

turfaco.com
maojod.com
gardensdiar.com
tasahel.net
gamma-international.com
matrixclouds.com
elkasrawyauto.com
matrixtranslation.com
server-egy.com
pf-uae.com
callforatrip.com

Languages

English – C2 Arabic – A1